### **AKVINDER KAUR 425-770-1518**

## **Professional Summary**

Executive Assistant with 5+ years of experience in office management, administrative support, project support and management, that thrives in fast paced environment. Multi-talented with skills in several creative mediums, including marketing, event planning, and coordinating. I have consistently excelled myself with various projects to the satisfaction of clients within tight time limit and budget. Knowledgeable in handling confidential matters with appropriate guidelines.

#### Skills

Superb attention to Details Excellent in Visio

Excellent Communication skills

Project Presentations

Outstanding in Microsoft Word

Outstanding in PowerPoint

Great Leadership Skills

Excellent in SharePoint

Complex Problem Solving

Outstanding in Microsoft Excel

Time management

Customer service-oriented

## **Work History**

Executive Administrative Assistant Scotsman Guide Media – Bothell, WA 11/2018 to 05/2020

- · Oversee all administrative operations, manage every aspect of project development, from vendors to sales orders. Established a successful organizational and filing system.
- · Generated new ideas with limited directions and varied internal client needs.
- · Worked with internal clients to determine strategy and design.
- Researched and collaborated with various vendors that satisfy client's demand.
- Presented various projects ideas as well as implementing the overall demands of the client.
- · Creating PowerPoint presentations to enhance and confirm the overall image of the client's vision of the project.
- Decision making by considering the cost and benefit of ideas and applying the appropriate one.
- · Coordinate space and color planning with client's choice.
- Ability to complete project within the budget implemented by client with satisfaction.

Administrative Coordinator/Marketing

06/2016 to 09/2018

- The Blind Alley Bellevue, WA
  - · Assisted with event planning and project management.
  - · Collaborated with vendors and clients to ensure style consistency and theme.
  - · Maintained calendars and schedules.
  - Ability to generate new ideas with selective and limited options and directions.
  - · Utilize social media to promote events and programs.
  - Proficient in data collection, entry and maintenance.
  - · Assist with arrangements and preparation of events and meetings.
  - · Ability to think and resolve situations at the last minute.
  - · Has an Eye for artistic and unique details as well as ideas.

Client Area Representative

07/2014 to 03/2016

IOD Incorporated - Bellevue, WA

- Translated complex concepts and data into compelling visuals for media outreach.
- ullet Designed new on-brand visual elements to effectively convey concepts and messaging.
- · Collaborated with vendors to ensure style consistency with other marketing materials.
- Presented projects to internal clients.
- · Coordinated translation of labels and sales materials.
- · Carefully proofread labels and sales materials prior to printing.
- · Ability to strategize in order to complete projects productively and efficiently.

# Education

Bachelor of Arts: Psychology Argosy University - Seattle, WA

sy University - Seattle, WA 2012